Finding Aid for the Davida Rochlin Papers LSC.2369
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 6: The New American Porch pop-up show, 2010
  - About the architect/artist statement, circa 2010 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - National Public Radio "Summer on the Porch" article, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Publicity, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Porch slide descriptions, circa 2010 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Exhibition materials, circa 2010 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Pop-up show digital exhibition materials, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    This folder contains 2 CDs labeled "Porch exhibit final print 7-30-10 files" and "The New Front Porch exhibition 7/23/10 DRAIA finished photos."
  - Porch type blurbs, circa 2010 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Porch slides (photographs), 1997-2010 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Pop-up porch show wall signage, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Pop-up show wall signage, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - The New American Porch oversize exhibit photographs, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Series 7: Digital materials, 1994-2010; 1981-2010 (Box 50, Box 51)
  This series contains unprocessed digital material, primarily CAD drawings. Included are 305 3.5 inch floppy disks, 2 5.25 inch floppy disks, and 6 CDs. Known file types include .dwg, .dxf, .kad, .pdf, .plt, .tiff, and .txt. See attached spreadsheet for a list of specific projects and additional information.
  Other Finding Aids
  A digital copy of the digital materials inventory is available via this link: Link to Davida Rochlin papers digital materials inventory